babiesonline.com 2008-06-17

# Privacy Statement for BabiesOnline.com, INC

## Privacy Statement for BabiesOnline.com, INC

BabiesOnline.com, INC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: BabiesOnline.com, INC.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other purposes.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. **BabiesOnline.com, INC** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email and postal address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and to provide to select birth product marketers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email and postal address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Children's Guidelines

According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program.

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. To unsubscribe from our mailing list please visit http://www.babiesonline.com/forms/newsletters/unsubscribe.asp
  2. To delete your member account and your baby's web page, visit http://www.babiesonline.com/forms/contact and send a request that includes the email address registered to your account and four-digit PIN. 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. Email us via our Contact Form

## Third Party Advertising

We use DoubleClick's Network, Sonar, and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here [ http://www.sonar.com/naiprivacy](http://www.sonar.com/naiprivacy). 

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

You can immediately opt-out of Doubleclick's unique cookies and have it switched to a non-unique cookie by clicking here [ http://www.doubleclick.net/cgi-bin3/optout/check2.pl](http://www.doubleclick.net/cgi-bin3/optout/check2.pl). You will find more information on opting out of Doubleclick's cookies can be found at <http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm>. If for some reason your cookies are erased, you will need to opt-out again. Please also check the privacy policy page at all the major advertising networks. You can find many of these by searching on google.com with the keywords: privacy policy advertising network 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Shannon Anderson BabiesOnline.com, INC P.O. Box 16858 Albuquerque, NM 87191 Email Us
